# autumn jung

autumnkangas@gmail.com · 312-888-0342

GitHub: AutumnJ · Website: autumnj.github.io

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### **LANGUAGES**

JavaScript

Ruby

Python

HTML

CSS

SOL

#### FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

Ruby on Rails

Sinatra

iQuery

React

Redux

Bootstrap

Django

#### **TESTING**

RSpec

Mocha

Capybara

#### **PERSISTENCE**

**SQLite** 

PostgreSQL

#### OTHER

Git, Sublime Text, Fiddler, Postman, PythonAnywhere Full stack web developer with a passion for natural and programming languages. With experience in Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, and React, and a background in office management, I discovered web development while working at various tech startups. I bring strong skills in project management and a desire for iterative innovation, which helps companies provide the best product and experience to their clients and employees.

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

#### PETS SEEKING PEOPLE

#### GitHub | Ruby Gem

Command line interface scraper gem to locate cats and dogs available for adoption by geographic location

- Scraped ASPCA website with Nokogiri and bundled results into CLI gem
- Published to RubyGems (900+ downloads)

#### **COMMUNITY LIBRARY**

#### GitHub | Demo

Rails application for tracking books in your library, and lending or borrowing books from others

- Built application with MVC pattern and internal API, using Rails and JavaScript to power the front end
- Used OmniAuth for OAuth authentication via GitHub and Devise for authenticating other users
- Leveraged ¡Query and JavaScript for AJAX functionality

#### ADOPT A PET

#### GitHub | Demo

Gamified adoptable pet search interface with React front end and Rails back end

- Incorporated user inputs into external API request (Petfinder) and persisted returned data to internal Rails API
- Managed application state with Redux
- Used Bootstrap's React-Bootstrap implementation for design elements

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JELLYVISION - Chicago, IL

#### Software Quality Assurance Contractor | 9/2017-12/2017

- Executed cross browser and mobile device testing for Flash and HTML-based applications
- Verified required functionality and customizations based on client-specific healthcare and benefits enrollment options
- Compiled detailed bug report documentation and worked with development team (using JIRA and confluence) to test subsequent fixes

#### CONFERENCES

Google Women Techmakers Women's Day Summit MARCH 2018

GOTO Chicago Software Developer Conference APRIL 2018

#### REVIEWTRACKERS - Chicago, IL

#### Office Manager | 7/2017-9/2017

- Created and implemented operational budget for office events, supplies, services, and amenities
- Provided executive support for VP of Operations, COO and CEO of tech startup with 50+ employees

## HEALTHCARE RESEARCH (MYCNAJOBS) - Chicago, IL Office Manager and Executive Assistant to CEO | 5/2015-7/2017

- Managed all incoming revenue, including executing accounts receivable and payable tasks in QuickBooks, processing and scheduling recurring credit card payments and implementing client-specific collections procedures
- Administered payroll and benefits for healthcare tech startup as it grew from 10 to 35 employees
- Moved HR documentation for all past and present employees to online platform (BambooHR) to reduce liability
- Used Zoho and HubSpot CRMs to manage client records
- Built wireframes with Mockflow and performed requirements mapping for creation of proprietary CRM and billing system

## RAVENSWOOD HEALTH AND WELLNESS CENTER - Chicago, IL Office Manager and Chiropractic Assistant | 2/2014-5/2015

- Created and implemented employee manual and training procedures for 10 chiropractic assistants
- Managed weekly schedule of 200+ appointments while providing administrative support to chiropractors and registered nurse
- Handled all payments for practice, including verifying insurance coverage, communicating payment plans and issuing invoices

### CP HOMES/PACRIM INTERNATIONAL CAPITAL - Shenzhen, China Assistant to the General Manager's Office | 7/2012-3/2013

- Utilized Mandarin Chinese skills to assist Chinese-speaking HR team in their efforts to recruit an English-speaking lawyer
- Translated company policies from Chinese to English
- Compiled monthly client-facing newsletter and translated articles from English to Mandarin Chinese
- Prepared clients for the EB-5 visa process by conducting mock interviews
- Researched and compiled location-specific transition materials to prepare Chinese clients for a successful cultural, economic and social transition to the United States

#### **EDUCATION**

#### FLATIRON SCHOOL

#### Full Stack Web Development Program | 2018

• Women Take Tech Scholarship Recipient

#### SHENZHEN UNIVERSITY

Shenzhen. China

Certificate: Chinese Language | 2011-2012

#### LIBERTY UNIVERSITY ONLINE

#### Bachelor of Arts in Biblical Studies | 2011

• Graduated Summa Cum Laude